LÊ VĂN HÙNG

Java Backend Staff



Contact information

- **10/03/1995**
- Nam
- 0326817904
- hunglvpd05295@fpt.edu.vn
- 🦀 🖰 Đà Nẵng
- https://github.com/ITBusy

Skills

Front-end

- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- Jquery, Bootstrap 5
- Angular Cli
- Ajax jquery
- ReactJS

Database

- My Sql,
- MS Sql Server,
- Firebase

Mobile

- React native

Backend

- Java, OOP, JDBC, Jsp & Serverlet,
Hibernate, Jpa, Spring boot

English

Can read English documents

Career goals

I am a final year student majoring in Information Technology in Java Backend. With the professional knowledge that has been learned, I want to find the right internship job that is the position of java backend staff and promote my ability well. The practical work experience you have accumulated will be the basis for you to achieve your goal of becoming a good network management expert in the next 5 years.

Education

FPT Polytechnic College

10/2020-Now

Software Technology

Final year students

Work experience

Sales website

02/2022-05/2022

FPT Polytechnic College

- Link: https://github.com/ITBusy/Laptopshop.git
- Number of members: Individual
- Technology performed: spring boot, ajax, html, css
- Functional description: CRUD

Sales website 2

05/2022-07/2022

FPT Polytechnic College

- Link backend spring boot: https://github.com/ITBusy/backend.git
- Link Frontend Angular Cli: https://github.com/ITBusy/website-sales.git
- Number of members: Individual
- Technology performed: spring boot, angular cli, firebase, jwt security, html, css
- Functional description: CRUD, put image on firebase, security by jwt

Other projects:

10/2020-Now

FPT Polytechnic College

Link: https://github.com/ITBusy